Hello all our theatre and investor brothers
welcome today we are going to talk
about the results of ICICI Lombard General Insurance we
will discuss in a little more detail after that we will
see that this can be done that's why
we put a lot of hard work in this video so please
subscribe our channel by clicking on the
bell icon so that you get all the updates
of our channel so
friends we are here
on the Q3 results of ICICI Lombard we will
compare it quarter by quarter
death 2nd year and near World Twenty20
so the number here is 478 lakh so
we will consider it like this but for us to
read so that you understand
for comparison we will
grease it by doing 478 like this so the first number 6
point which you are seeing is the total income
dowry if you check it from the previous quarter
then it is 318 and the total income of five gas
is big if you reduce it then it was 305
subscribe big if you
take out the total subscribe so we have  Here the
total expenses have increased a lot
compared to the previous quarter and
share, so as you can see 358
friends, free lesson on point number 3
compared to the previous quarter which is
330.5 and previous year mother 274, so here the
total expenses have increased a lot
and in that condition we are not seeing this total income which has
increased so much, so it has been
interesting to learn what these
profit after tax results are, so
effective after everything - Justin Lemon
language, we are going into details,
so you will see the profit here, here the
profit after tax number-27, here you
can see a very disappointing
performance, you can say after provisioning,
take 500 3101, you have their profit
after tax in 2017 which is the last one death
of t4, so here there is an ignore from the road and
team and if you reduce it, friend and
near then  He just matched it
and even at 31st it is still 31, so I
think the results are not that good here
and by increasing it, yes-yes liquid liner a little but
if you look at the points then it is 2.5 feet,
he subscribed
600, if you talk about expense of
management of
20 celebs in this, then I
think I have definitely seen a little bit here
even today and subscribe
friends, we will go further
on this and as you can see, a Shahrukh
setting has come in this topic, SIM September
2016, so here it was straight
605, from there it went to the lower side
3151, so it was around 400 points,
after that I upvoted this post, so
one
subscribe here
and since last two days it is
waiting a little due to profit booking, so if you are not subscribed, then
subscribe on the side line, so
subscribe if you
get it around zero 135 use, then
you can bike there, this top and from
there the stop can go 1015 has coming
Days if any good news comes
in the stock then solve with this point, don't think it is a very
good time to go in the
stock, but if it reaches this level then make
resistance in this lot here friends, it can
go up to this level, so
put it in it so that you
can see a level from there, it has been formed here, if you
test this level here then it will be of
number one or this neck line of 06,
if
pregnant it can definitely
go up to next sure,
stop at Gabbar, this line which is below the trend line,
if follow sign is given on one day
chart then you have to unite there, so the
risk is very very minimal, so
below this trend line like the project
gives users to stop loss and you
can exit, so I think you have a very good
relationship, this stock on MNREGA item, you will
get this share, so digest from outside,
if you are new to the channel then subscribe
and press the bell icon, if you have joined the channel
yet but have not pressed the bell
icon to do and word press the bell icon
because  After that you will start getting updates from
our channel.